Well, just the other day, he let me braid it, too.
You are a one-wit boy, aren't you?
Oh, wow.
Your pigtails are straight-up cute.
I love your hair like that.
Yeah, you should rock that dew every single day.
I'm guessing Hori did it for you, right?
It's adorable.
This look is totes perfect for your bone structure.
Oh, there goes the bow.
See you tomorrow.
Hey, you can't help, he's pretty!
Come on, dummy. We're leaving.
Now hold on, Hori.
Do you want to know what you want?
live
um
is
Thank you.
Soは言えない元通りにはもうできない
あの子に隠した本物はどこ
怒ってくれない分かってくれない
思ってもただ募ってしまうだけ
懐かしい匂いとこの歌が残る
ホティ?
Can I please have my bag?
Are you mad at me?
Because of those girls?
They got under your skin that much?
I have every right to be mad!
They all treated you as if you were invisible before!
But the second you cut your dumb hair
they can't keep their eyes or their paws off you
and shamelessly flirt right in front of me!
I'm not bothered in the least.
Are you sure?
My point is that I think you should stop it
He's depressing
Whoa, good eye, Taniyata
So, Mr. Doom and Gloom turned prep?
That does seem to be the case
So, you doing alright these days?
Yeah
Damn, you sure hit a growth spurt
And holy shit, your piercings?
You don't look so bad yourself, Taniyata
Yeah, don't say my name
Hearing it from your mouth skews me out
It took you till high school to grow a pair?
Loser
Ha ha, what's this?
You have some stupid chick carry your bag around?
Hey, show some respect
That stupid chick might be his girlfriend
You really scored if she is
Ten out of ten would bone
What's wrong, cat guy your tongue?
Are the two of you finished yet?
Oh, she speaks
So you his girlfriend or not?
Do you know what he was like back in middle school?
Imagine the most emo loner you've ever seen in your entire life
Just pathetic
Hey
Huh?
I asked you a question you failed to answer
Are you finished?
Uh-huh
If so, then you assholes can piss off
Well, I was in a pretty cruddy mood to begin with
So that was bad timing on their part
I mean
They were treating you like crap for no reason
How else was I supposed to react?
Right
Seriously though
I can't believe how nasty those idiots were
Yeah
Great
Will that be all for you today?
Dang, Tanihara
Did you take up martial arts or something?
I had a run-in with Miyamura
Really?
Oof
If he's the one picking on you now
I guess the shoe's on the other foot
That's whatever, man
He wasn't alone for once
He had some girl with him
I think they might even be dating
Any idea who I'm talking about?
Some girl, huh?
Oh
You must mean Hori
He actually landed himself a girl
You know
You should probably stop teasing him like you did when we were younger
Since he met Hori, his defense stats have been no joke
She is girlfriend or a summon from an RPG?
He says it's whatever
But it keeps bothering him
The guy just can't seem to get Miyamura out of his head
Does it hurt?
Huh?
Does what hurt?
Never mind
Just
Thank you
Thank you?
Where is this coming from?
I'm lucky enough to have someone who gets mad on my behalf
She's right by my side
I know
Use your open hand
Make it the smallest slap ever
No, Hori
Why not?
It wouldn't be the first time you've done it, right?
Just pull back and bam
I already told you no
Oh, I'm begging you
One small slap
That is the least slappable face ever
She's all but down on her knees
So why keep denying her?
Where the hell did you come from, Shindo?
Over there, bro
I was stalking you from afar, but
You were treating Hori in such a despicable manner that I had to jump in
Some man you are
You were stalking me?
It's none of your business, Shindo
So just butt out
I don't know what's going on here
But I bet it's sexual
Why's that the first place your mind went to?
What's the big deal?
Does my happiness not matter because you fell out of love with me?
No, of course not
Poor Hori
Your boyfriend's a poophead
Why are you still here?
If I can fulfill your wish instead, then I'm at your service
No task is too great
Unless you don't want me
Nope
It's totally pointless if it's not me and Morda
Which would mean that it is something sexual?
How do you get your brain to function without any cells in it?
I've had just about enough
Come on, let's go
Hori?
You can be louder
Why me?
Move your ass or I'll make you
Not what it looks like
Get your mind out of the gutter
Uh, got it
Ooh, can we stop by the convenience store on the way?
Sure
You dumb hoe
What the actual hell?
Tanihada
You've got extra cash, so buy me a drink
I'm thirsty
Get your own damn drink, you leech
What's wrong, buddy?
That stick-too-farb ass
Shut up
Hey, goon squad
Stop loitering in the parking lot
Huh?
Uh, we can do whatever the hell we want to, bitch
It's a summon from the underworld
If you want to take that crap attitude out
Hey, don't talk to this girl like that, you freaking moron
Damn, what you yelling at me for?
It's all gravy
Just wanted to clean up the trash around here
Keeping it green for both you and me
Oh, you're recycling?
Good work, guys
Damn, that was close
If you had kept talking, that demonic woman would have bashed all our skulls in for sure
What? Really?
She's that tough?
Hey, look, it's Miyamura
I swear, the next time I see that guy alone, I'll-
Oh!
That guy's as much of a monster as she is
Holy shit
So, um, you guys want to talk about it or nah?
I'm not one to kink shame, but
This makes me wonder if she's right in the head
You've had your fun, but listen
Fine, you win
I think it'd be best to just put all this out of my mind
Miyamura sure changed in the last few years
High school transformation?
More like reincarnation
I mean, you remember how he was back in middle school
He barely talked to us
Now he's going around hitting girls
Shit
I'm leaving
Huh? You are? It's still early, man
Damn it
I'm home
Okay, catch you later
Bye?
Yo, be back by dinner, capisce?
And you're still here because
I thought I went without saying
But this is my house too
Hey, um, sir
Would you mind if I ask for some advice?
Nope
Sure don't
Way too eager
Very sus
Shut it
A man-to-man talk has nothing to do with you
So what's up?
You good?
Why are we in the bathroom?
Um, I'm fine, thanks
But I have a question regarding Horty
Oh, no, don't tell me she's preggers yet again
What do you mean, yet again?
No, sir, nothing like that
She just really loves it when I get mad and yell at her
And I have no clue why
What the?
Better kink or something?
One would assume
I wonder
You don't normally yell
It's like a bizarro you
Bizarro?
Like if you cleaned up and went to the office
Your wife might be into that change?
Ouch, man
But yeah
It's kind of a different flavor of you
That makes sense
I hate to break up whatever it is you're doing in here
But I also want to bathe at a decent hour
Sit down
You should be a part of this talk, too
No, thanks
Kyoko, your boyfriend's sad and worried and you don't even care
You are such a pain
Want to know what's a pain?
Trying to live up to your irrational expectations
Hold the phone
You are the last person I want to hear a lecture from
Maybe you could try doing some chores before you nag on people for being inconsiderate
Shots fired
Right in my feelings
The curry I made the other day should count for something
Know what it counts for?
The amount of time it took to microwave it
But you said it was yummy
Well, yeah, of course
Pre-packaged stuff is always good
Oh, and Sota got seconds, remember?
Why is this water the perfect temperature?
Ah, oh, you're sopping wet
Better nix those clothes
Wait, please, sir
Stop unzipping my boyfriend
Give you three guesses what you and I did for fun the other day
No way
Those pop songs are too hard, dude
It got old fast
If it ain't traditional or rap, you won't sing
Yeah, but he listens to everything
Which is why he could have busted out western stuff, too
Yo, Mizuuchi
You...
Wanna be a jerk and ignore me?
Sorry
But it's because I'm here
Apparently
He has a little crush on Hori, so
Oh, wow
Does everyone at this school like her?
But my eyes have been opened to the truth
One does not simply fall in love with Kiroko Hori
Hey, where is she?
I think the student council room
My phone's missing
Did you leave it in a science lab?
One way to find out
Huh?
No?
I, uh, think I left my phone
Have you seen it lying around anywhere?
No
Okay
Why would your phone be with the supplies?
Well, nobody else had class in this room since we did
So it's gotta be around here somewhere
Unless it sprouted legs and walked away
What's your number?
Huh?
I'll call it
Uh, really?
Um, yeah, okay
It's zero nine zero
Then
Found it
What?
You had it in your back pocket the entire time
Thanks for the help
He saved the day
Huh?
Hang on
Why is the screen all black?
Then you go and break it less than three seconds later?
Why did she choose a dimwit like you?
I
I take that back
Question for you
If you had no choice
Do
Do you think you could punch Hori?
Punch her?
Like
If we were fighting?
Uh
Yeah
Let's go with that
Um
No
I'd never raise a hand to her
I see
If that's the case
You and her wouldn't have worked out anyway
Hey, there you are
Find your phone?
Oh
Yeah
You really do leave it everywhere
You would probably lose your head too if it wasn't attached, huh?
Well, maybe make a mental note to check next time if
You can make a mental note to check your mouth!
Does that sound like a plan?
Now move
Mizuuchi
Leave her be
Um
K
Listen
You know
You're so quiet and scrawny that I didn't think you were the kind of guy that could stand up for himself
The term loser comes to mind
But now that you're together with Hori
I see how confident you are
Yep, sure am
Dude
Why are your eyes all red and puffy?
Were you rubbing them or something?
Miyamura
Get out!
There's not enough room!
And where should I go?
Outside of here!
Speaking of, where the heck are we?
We are outside
What?
This place is outside
The only free space there is
I'm not dumb
I know what a locker looks like
And the only things missing are the textbooks
But this is what it's like outside
This is how it feels
You've always been on the inside
So it's a feeling that's unfamiliar to you
Who gives a damn?
All this inside-outside nonsense is stupid
You realize you're the one who brought it up, right?
I'm just answering the questions you have
We've never really talked like this before
Do tight spaces make you uneasy?
Yeah, I hate them
Hmm
That makes two of us
You enjoy being on the inside?
I mean
It's better than this
Even if
There's no one to enjoy it with?
Huh?
If everybody on the inside decided they wanted to try things outside
You'd be left alone in there
Well
You don't care if you're in or out
What you're focused on is whether or not people are with you
That makes or breaks your preference
The people on your side are what matter to you
Simple as that
I just
Um
Huh?
Miyamura's number?
What?
What do you want it for?
None of your business
Just tell me
Fine, I'll text it to you
The rabbits liked Miyamura better than anyone
Everybody and their grandma knew
Back then
What the?
Where did this rabbit tangent come from?
More importantly, how long does it take to text a friggin' number?
He's ignoring me
Izumi?
Since you're near the door, can you bring the sign in?
On it
You guys closed already?
Sorry
We're closed tomorrow too, but we'll be open the day after
You may be in luck
There's another shop
A little further
It's a much bigger bakery and still open
If you turn that corner there
Something from this cake shop
Oh
Are you sure?
But
It's okay
I'll stop by again the day after tomorrow
I hear your cheesecake's good?
It's very good
Cool
See you in two days
Enjoy the break
And our fruit tarts are awesome
Try those too
If you want
All right
I'm sold
I'll get two of each
Got it
I'll save them for you
Later
But not too much
I tried to call
Myself?
I broke it the other day
I'm gonna try and get it fixed tomorrow
Uh
Okay
So I guess he wasn't purposely ignoring me
It's been the other way around
I was ignoring him
All this time
Did it stress you out?
What?
Um
I
Never mind
Bye
For real
Tanihara
Sorry we're closed
But thanks for coming
I forgot to feed the rabbits
I know I was supposed to
But by summer's end
They were all dead
They starved
After I blamed the entire thing on you
I blamed you but
It's my fault
Okay
Miyamura
I've been wanting to tell you
I'm sorry
I wonder
How would things
Have turned out
If I'd apologized back then
It hurts my heart
To think about it
Okay
That was the last one
Thanks a million for helping me
Hmm
Are these your old yearbooks?
Yeah
That one's from middle school
Good times
What did she look like in those days?
Peek and you die where you sit
Your books are kind of annoying
Aren't they?
They're bulky
And take up lots of space
On your shelves
But throwing them away
Feels wrong for some reason
Did you toss yours?
Or do you still have them?
I wanted to trash them
But then I felt how heavy they were
And I had that dilemma
You just mentioned
So
I wound up keeping them
And I'm glad I did
Because my past experiences
Shaked me into the person
I am now
I'm sure Miyamura
Must have wanted to throw
A lot more than his yearbooks away
I don't know the details
Of what he went through
In middle school
From what I've gathered though
I suspect he might have
Hated everything
Aimlessly drifting along
With no purpose
But now it's different
Now he can look back
And be happy
That he didn't throw
Everything away
Well
All this talk of yearbooks
Makes me wonder
How our senior one's
Gonna turn out
Yeah
But no way of knowing
Until we get it
I took the pictures in April
But it seems like forever ago
I guess it kinda does
I hope they get a shot
Of me with Mizuuchi
What?
You're joking, right?
No
We recently bonded
Believe it or not
Wow
The one good thing
To come from losing my cell phone
He was mean to me before
But we're on better
Turns
At least I think so
Is that his kink?
What's even crazier
Is that things are starting
To look promising
With Tanihara too
That is crazy
Even if it's difficult
First starting out
I think you have the potential
To be friends with anybody
It's hard
But not impossible
Interesting
Chinese
I think the future
Ooh
Because so
To be friends with them
Folk
Ak
not
the
no
Golden
comes
far
a
like
otz
ou
ni
言葉にできないんだけどね